I have so many things on my mind.
I have so many things to do.
And the one I'm sacrificing is you.
Just do everything you need to do first.
But once you're done,
you'll take me all over the world.
Who did this?
They're outsiders.
And with interest.
Not just for you,
but for Mikoy too.
Just investigate this.
I'll handle it, sir.
Uh, Dara…
I'll be back.
Bok.
What was Mikoy bugging you about?
Nothing.
He was just asking for relationship advice
for him and Chiara.
He asked you for relationship advice?
For his relationship with Chiara?
Wow!
He wanted to do
something special for Chiara.
And as a woman,
he was asking me what I would like.
Of all people, you're the one he asked
for that kind of advice?
Someone like you,
who don't have a single
romantic bone in your body?
And you don't have a proper relationship.
And you also have no idea
what a dating scene looks like.
And most of all,
you're stiffer than a log.
That's not true.
And I can also be romantic.
So, let's go?
I just saw a newly opened theme park.
The rides there are amazing.
-Wow!
-What?
-Should we check it out?
-A theme park?
I'm guessing
you probably even had
the whole theme park closed.
Just so you could have me all to yourself.
And there will be a fireworks display.
to make it more romantic.
Was that really your plan?
Erase! Pretend I didn't say anything.
Pretend I don't know.
I just wanted to surprise you.
How was I supposed to know?
You're so rich.
You've probably experienced
almost everything already.
You already have it all.
It's hard to think of something.
So here it is.
I'm trying to do the K-drama way.
See?
You're even laughing at me.
-I know it's cheesy.
-I'm not laughing at you.
I'm actually happy.
Because as they say,
it's the thought that counts!
Because you thought of me,
of course, I'm also feeling giddy.
I don't need you to do
K-drama romantic gestures.
Just being with you
is more than enough for me.
All right.
Since you ruined my surprise,
I thought of a much better place to go.
What?
Do you want to see a real hippopotamus?
At the zoo?
Hopeless, maybe, but romantic, Bok?
I doubt it. Okay?
-Go ahead. Keep teasing me.
-Come on.
You really can't take a joke.
All right.
What advice did you give?
You know, what women want
is actually simple.
There's no need for grand gestures
just to make us feel important
to our partner.
You're actually listening to me now, Bok.
Hey.
Why does it seem like
you don't trust the advice you gave?
I just feel sorry for Mikoy.
He still believes that
when all things are said and done,
and when all of this is over,
his relationship with Chiara will survive.
You never know.
Maybe Chiara will understand
what Mikoy did, right?
You don't understand.
I strongly believe that Chiara herself
has something to do with the Moravianos.
MANILA ZOOLOGICAL & BOTANICAL GARDEN
Madam.
If you have a zoo in Prague,
our zoo here in Manila is even better.
But our zoo here is… for men only.
Man-ila Zoo!
Come on. Come on.
The very famous Ma'ali!
It is cute, right?
But you know what?
All elephants are female.
They're female.
Because if they were male,
they'd be "ele-brief".
Let's go, Medusa? Come on. Let's go.
Wow!
So, did you know that zebra…
What? That they're all female?
Huh?
Because "she", then "bra".
So, it's "she-bra".
No!
Because they always complain
whenever people take photos of them.
They say there's no color.
It's all black and white.
Do you know her name?
What?
Blythe. Black and white.
Hi, Blythe!
Don't take a picture of that anymore.
Did you know?
They're the most useless animal.
Because…
"Wa-lion".
Rawr!
It's not moving.
Is it dead?
Oh… "Buhay-ya".
But you know,
they often get misunderstood.
Their reputation was ruined
because of those politicians
and all the corrupt people.
They are the most honest of all.
Because if they really want to eat you,
they'll eat you right away.
Just kidding.
Mr. Pinagpala, don't you have
any trivia now?
You know,
they're the most misunderstood of all.
They're only judged
because they were the ones
who tempted Eve and Adam.
That's why we got kicked out of paradise.
But the question is…
Who ate the apple?
Wasn't it also a human?
Are they just misunderstood
because they can't speak?
What if it's a person?
What if… What if
it was a person who betrayed them?
Can you still call them a snake?
Why are you telling me this?
You're betraying me, aren't you?
Hey.
Why are you so serious?
You know, you're cuter when you're joking.
Even if it's corny.
Let's go.
I don't know about you.
It's up to you.
You, seriously!
What do you need this time?
There are actually some people
who want to say sorry to you.
Who?
Hurry! So slow!
Angelito, I just wanted
to apologize to you.
Me and my boys are…
asking for your forgiveness.
-Sorry.
-We're really sorry.
Oh, right, the plates.
Don't do or finish them anymore.
I'll do it myself.
-We will do it.
-We'll help him.
You're right, so we can learn.
-Me.
-Just him.
Right.
But it feels like something's missing.
-Right?
-Missing?
-Payment.
-I don't have money!
Let's just give money!
Hurry! You're taking too long!
It's not part of our agreement.
This is our payment for all your effort.
That's not necessary.
No! Come on.
-Accept it, Angelito.
-Right.
An apology is worthless
-without reparations.
-It's nothing.
-So, accept it.
-Right.
-Correct.
-Just accept the money.
Wait a minute.
Wow!
‎What?
This is a birthday gift from my dad.
‎Hey, don't.
So you won't be late for class.
You'll always be aware of the time.
-Hurry!
-That's left.
-Right.
-Owen James Nicholas.
-JC Ferrer.
Say it properly.
Because if we do it again…
-Because if we do it again…
…and we bully again…
-…and we bully again…
-What?
-I don't like.
Hurry! Answer!
Sorry.
-I am dead.
Zebra!
So, what animal wears briefs?
What?
They're so cute, right?
But seriously, there's a story
about lovebirds.
When those birds fall in love,
they choose one bird in the whole world,
and for their whole life,
they stay with it,
wherever it goes.
And they will never leave
each other's side.
They will follow it anywhere.
Even if it's far,
even if it's dangerous.
They can't even survive
without each other.
So cute, right?
That's why they're called lovebirds.
Because that's really how they love.
A mime.
Oh, he's calling me. Okay.
-That's so sweet!
-I wish I have that one, too!
‎Sweet!
Let's go. Come with me.
-There?
-Yes.
I don't want to. It's embarrassing.
Don't be shy anymore.
Because you're "mime".
Kiss!
Just kidding.
Why are you here again?
Oh, why?
Aren't we okay now?
After everything I did for you.
-What are you saying?
-Right?
I fixed your problem with your bullies.
So, I expected that
you'd let me hang out here.
Okay, Sofie.
I appreciate what you did
to Owen and the boys.
I'm actually impressed by your courage.
But Sofie, you can't always
hang out here in my dorm.
Don't you have anywhere to stay?
Are you homeless?
I'm not homeless.
I just really have a problem with my room.
I already complained
to the building administrator,
but no one has answered yet.
So, it left me with no choice.
So what? You just trespassed
into someone else's room?
So I just explored other options.
You know, I don't get it.
There are so many rooms here.
So why did you choose mine?
What if I were a bad guy?
What if I were a rapist
and took advantage of you?
Do you think I can't defend myself?
From the first time I saw you,
I already knew you're not someone
who can even break a glass.
You know so much.
I'll just do this so that
you'll stop bothering me.
Do you know how to do that?
Of course.
Oh!
What are you doing? Your damaging it more!
-Wait.
-My stuff!
What's happening?
I'm sorry.
-Are you okay?
-Sorry.
Wow! Wow! Oh, no!
My dear is like… magnificent!
Something like that.
-I just went out with Mikoy.
-Am I right?
You don't need to verbalize it
because I can see
the twinkle in your eyes.
You're laughing?
It's humanizing that
you're spending time with Mikoy.
You know, Mom.
I spent the whole day with him,
and it was just endless
corny pickup lines.
I never thought I'd be able to appreciate
that kind of humor.
Do you know what it's called?
Love.
There. You're happy when you're with him.
Let's not go that far.
How do you think
I survived your dad all these years?
Think about it.
I'm not a patient person.
But when I met him, I learned to…
endure a lot.
Was it easy for you when…
you found out the truth about dad?
That… he's not just
an ordinary businessman?
I'm going to sleep now.
Are you sure?
Your hair is still wet.
You might get a headache.
What are you talking about?
You know what? Just go to sleep too.
Here.
Wait, what are you doing?
-Going to sleep.
-No.
Just sleep here beside me.
-Beside you?
-Yes.
Why? Is there a problem?
Are you going to take advantage of me?
No!
Do you have a girlfriend
who will get jealous?
-None.
-No problem then.
Just sleep here beside me.
So you can sleep comfortably.
I'll just fix this.
What are you waiting for? Go to sleep.
Okay.
Easy?
Dear, with this beauty.
From Mabalacat, Pampanga.
Then I just ended up in a syndicate.
But…
I wanted to run away.
To the point that…
I wanted to forget him.
I wanted to… I wanted to open my mind,
so I could remove him from my memory.
That he exists.
Because I love him.
I can't leave him.
I can't turn away from him.
And I realized that's how it is, my dear.
You'll endure everything.
You'll face everything.
Just for the person you love.
So, my dear,
if Mikoy truly loves you,
he will accept you no matter who you are.
Whoever you may be. Okay?
Who is that?
Chiara Valtrovi. The daughter of Viktor.
And from what it looks like,
it seems the leader of Moraviano
will settle in the country.
And if my sources are correct,
they already bought a mansion in Fourbest.
Do we really need to drag
his daughter into this?
And they have already
crippled our operations!
If we kill his daughter,
it will send a clear
and unmistakable message.
Foreign syndicates are not welcome
in our country.
Only Filipinos are allowed
to deceive fellow Filipinos!
I didn't expect such a big change,
since you just started.
Thank you, sir. But that's nothing.
I just made a few adjustments
to our manpower.
To make our operations more efficient.
That's all.
Wow.
Chiara.
-Papa…
-It would be a pity.
He might become cold.
Hey!
Silly you!
No, we're just happy
with your performance, Mikoy.
Thank you.
I just don't want to disappoint you
with the trust you gave me.
I'll do my best for the company.
That's why we already discussed it.
We should have a party.
Something like a celebration!
What? A celebration?
That's not necessary.
It's like a welcoming party.
No need for a welcoming party.
I already feel very welcomed.
I feel more welcomed than "Rotonda".
You know what? You're funny!
Without even trying.
You're not the only main character
in this story. Come on.
What Mom is trying to say
It's time for the whole Philippines
to know
the Valtrovi family.
We need to smoke them out.
So we can eliminate those insects.
Just a reminder, Kian.
We are there as undercover agents.
Not to join the party.
But I guess
this is how it feels to hit the jackpot.
Chiara,
I just want you to know
that I will do everything for you.
Viktor!
Mikoy!